[{"answer": "Yes", "docId": "Basic-Instinct.txt", "asentId": 3, "question": "No.  We had a drink at the club. We left together.  I came here. He went home", "qsentId": 2}, {"answer": "No.  We had a drink at the club. We left together.  I came here. He went home", "docId": "Basic-Instinct.txt", "asentId": 5, "question": " No.  I wasn't in the mood to have sex with anyone last night", "qsentId": 4}, {"answer": " How about the coke", "docId": "Basic-Instinct.txt", "asentId": 7, "question": "No", "qsentId": 6}, {"answer": "Do you have a cigarette", "docId": "Basic-Instinct.txt", "asentId": 9, "question": "Yes, you do", "qsentId": 8}, {"answer": "You know all about me", "docId": "Basic-Instinct.txt", "asentId": 11, "question": " You know I don't like to wear any underwear, don't you, my friend", "qsentId": 10}, {"answer": "Come on, my friend.  You're not gonna let this slide.  What about her parents?  What about what else she's published?  At least we should get the stuff to see if we find anything else that's an amazing rea", "docId": "Basic-Instinct.txt", "asentId": 13, "question": "How did they die?  Was there an investigation", "qsentId": 12}, {"answer": "Maybe she did, my friend.  Maybe she grew herself an Afro and learned a left hook and put shoe polish on her face.  Let's polygraph her again and ask her about it", "docId": "Basic-Instinct.txt", "asentId": 15, "question": "Fuck you, too my friend", "qsentId": 14}, {"answer": "Maybe it's for ol", "docId": "Basic-Instinct.txt", "asentId": 17, "question": " He ain't that way.  He's got heart", "qsentId": 16}, {"answer": "No, sir.  You won't.  There's smoke off yonder on the horizon.  They're gonna want your badge", "docId": "Basic-Instinct.txt", "asentId": 19, "question": " You sure got real conclusive ways of demonstrating that", "qsentId": 18}, {"answer": " How exactly did you hear", "docId": "Basic-Instinct.txt", "asentId": 21, "question": " I don't know about that I don't have any money I don't have any attorneys my friend is my only real friend", "qsentId": 20}, {"answer": " I have attorneys.  They have friends.  I have friends.  Money buys you a lot of attorneys and friends", "docId": "Basic-Instinct.txt", "asentId": 23, "question": " I wasn't talking about real friends. Why doesn't Gus like me", "qsentId": 22}, {"answer": "What if I asked you not to call me Shooter", "docId": "Basic-Instinct.txt", "asentId": 25, "question": " My wife used to call me that", "qsentId": 24}, {"answer": " Forgive me for askin', son, and I don't mean to belabor the obvious, but why is it that you've got your head so far up your own ass", "docId": "Basic-Instinct.txt", "asentId": 27, "question": " Everybody that she plays with dies", "qsentId": 26}, {"answer": "Easy there, partner", "docId": "Basic-Instinct.txt", "asentId": 29, "question": " I wasn't there last night, either", "qsentId": 28}, {"answer": " You oughta use a rubber, pop.  You really should", "docId": "Basic-Instinct.txt", "asentId": 31, "question": " You don't like punk rockers", "qsentId": 30}, {"answer": "my friend and I talked to her at my friend's house.  All we did was write her name down", "docId": "Basic-Instinct.txt", "asentId": 33, "question": " Yeah.  But you didn't tell me to stay away from her car", "qsentId": 32}, {"answer": "My interest is in you, not in her. She seduces people, she manipulates", "docId": "Basic-Instinct.txt", "asentId": 35, "question": "I know the type.  I'm a psychologist", "qsentId": 34}, {"answer": "I decided to give you one more chance.  I missed you", "docId": "Basic-Instinct.txt", "asentId": 37, "question": "Did you miss me", "qsentId": 36}, {"answer": "Yeah, he said it was routine too. Now it's two guys saying it's routine", "docId": "Basic-Instinct.txt", "asentId": 39, "question": " Nope, can't say that I do", "qsentId": 38}, {"answer": "What kind of talk", "docId": "Basic-Instinct.txt", "asentId": 41, "question": "He had a girlfriend", "qsentId": 40}, {"answer": "What do you want, my friend?  Flowers? I'll send you some flowers", "docId": "Basic-Instinct.txt", "asentId": 43, "question": " The games are over.  You were right. It was the fuck of the century, Shooter", "qsentId": 42}]